China
Marist College
China
1789 1984
Marist Archives and Special Collections 3399 North Road, Poughkeepsie, New York 12601
Lowell Thomas
2.1.1.1.3
1203 linear feet
Items in this collection do not circulate and may be used in-house only.
China
- Lowell Thomas Papers
  - Graphic Materials, 2
    - Photographs, 2.1
      - Glass Plate Negatives, 2.1.1
        - Frank R. Roberson, 2.1.1.1
          - China, 2.1.1.1.3
              - Chinese Board of Punishment, 1/1/1914; 57 (Box 1174)
              - Execution of robbers, 1/1/1914; 58
              - Execution of robbers, 1/1/1914; 59
              - Execution of robbers, 1/1/1914; 60
              - Execution of robbers, 1/1/1914; 61
              - Chinese actors, 1/1/1914; 62
              - U.S.L.G. Peking, 1/1/1914; 1 (Box 1175)
              - Audience Chamber of the Forbidden City, 1/1/1914; 2
              - First throne of China, 1/1/1914; 3
              - Second throne of China, 1/1/1914; 4
              - Imperial OR Fifth throne of China, 1/1/1914; 5
              - Street scene, 1/1/1914; 6
              - Camp Lanzear (building where the experiments were made which proved that yellow fever is not transmitted by means of infected clothing), 1/1/1914; 7
              - Street scene, 1/1/1914; 8
              - Tree lined street, 1/1/1914; 9
              - Boats, 1/1/1914; 10
              - Three men, 1/1/1914; 11
              - Czarina of Russia, Undated; 12
              - Czarina of Russia, Undated; 13
              - Portrait of unidentified Western man, Undated; 14
              - Group of Chinese people, 1/1/1914; 15
              - Audience Chamber, Summer Palace, copy, 1/1/1914; 16
              - Camel back bridge, Summer Palace, copy, 1/1/1914; 17
              - Pagoda, Summer Palace, copy, 1/1/1914; 18
              - Marble boat, Summer Palace, copy, 1/1/1914; 19